{"metadata":{"generator":"Captivate","generatorVersion":"9.0.2","schemaVersion":"","author":"author","title":"","description":"project description","email":"author@company.com","website":"www.company.com","tags":"","thumbnail":"","source":"assets","durationInFrames":450,"frameRate":30,"totalSlides":8,"width":900,"height":380,"responsive":false,"scalable":false,"launchFile":"index.html"},"contentStructure":[{"id":"Title_AutoShape_5","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Title_AutoShape_5","title":"Knowledge Check ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"Text_Caption_145","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_145","title":"Choose the best answer for each of the following questions, then click “CHECK YOUR ANSWER” before continuing to the next question. ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"Button_25","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Button_25","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"}}},{"id":"si11032","class":"TODO::Senthil","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"}}},{"id":"si11046","class":"TODO::Senthil","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"}}},{"id":"SubTitle_AutoShape_5","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"SubTitle_AutoShape_5","title":"Activity ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"Slide10992","class":"Normal Slide","instance":"","thumbnail":"","children":["Text_Caption_145","Button_25","si11032","si11046"],"roles":{"slide":{"durationInFrames":180},"navigation":{"navid":"Slide10992"}}},{"id":"si7553","class":"TODO::Senthil","roles":{}},{"id":"si7473","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"Multiple Choice ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si7482","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"50,000 – 75,000 older people die each year due to drug-related problems (DRPs), making this the ____________ leading cause of death in older U.S. individuals.  ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si7497","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"A) ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si7501","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"First ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si7497_a","class":"TODO::Senthil","roles":{"answer":{"title":"First\r","index":"Not implemented","score":{"weight":0}}}},{"id":"si7508","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"B) ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si7512","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"Fifth ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si7508_a","class":"TODO::Senthil","roles":{"answer":{"title":"Fifth\r","index":"Not implemented","score":{"weight":10}}}},{"id":"si7980","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"C) ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si7984","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"Tenth ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si7980_a","class":"TODO::Senthil","roles":{"answer":{"title":"Tenth\r","index":"Not implemented","score":{"weight":0}}}},{"id":"si11404","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"D) ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si11408","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"Fifteenth ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si11404_a","class":"TODO::Senthil","roles":{"answer":{"title":"Fifteenth\r","index":"Not implemented","score":{"weight":0}}}},{"id":"si7557","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"Check Your Answer ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"submit","question":"Slide7447q0","for":"Slide7447q0"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si11703","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"Clear ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"clear","question":"Slide7447q0","for":"Slide7447q0"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si7894","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"Next Question ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"skip","question":"Slide7447q0","for":"Slide7447q0"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si10892","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"Back ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"back","question":"Slide7447q0","for":"Slide7447q0"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si7908","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"You must answer the question before continuing. ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si7912","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"Sorry, that’s incorrect.  Answer B is correct.  Please see Lesson 1, Topic 1, Page 2: Drug-Related Problems (DRPs).  Click “Next Question” to continue.  ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si7916","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"That’s Correct!  Click “Next Question” to continue.  ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si11695","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"Good try, but you have not selected the correct answer.  Please see Lesson 1, Topic 1, Page 2: Drug-Related Problems (DRPs).  Click here to continue, then click the “Clear” button to try again. ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"Slide7447","class":"Question Slide","instance":"","thumbnail":"","children":["si7473","si7482","si7501","si7512","si7984","si11408","si7557","si11703","si7894","si10892","si7908","si11695"],"roles":{"slide":{"durationInFrames":90},"navigation":{"navid":"Slide7447"},"question":{"interactionId":"7460","quizId":455,"title":"Multiple Choice\r","text":"50,000 – 75,000 older people die each year due to drug-related problems (DRPs), making this the ____________ leading cause of death in older U.S. individuals.\r\r","ikc":false,"type":"graded","interactionType":"choice","ramdomized":false,"correctAnswers":["B"],"score":{"weight":10,"penalty":0}}}},{"id":"si10708","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_140","roles":{}},{"id":"si10640","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_131","title":"Multiple Choice, Multiple Answers ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si10652","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_132","title":"Red flags for drug-related problems (DRPs) include: (select all that apply)   ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si10663","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_133","title":"A) ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si10667","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_134","title":"Patients seeing multiple doctors ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si10667","class":"TODO::Senthil","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button","question":"Slide10788q1"},"answer":{"title":"dummy title","index":-1,"score":{}}}},{"id":"si10663_a","class":"TODO::Senthil","roles":{"answer":{"title":"Patients seeing multiple doctors\r","index":"Not implemented","score":{"weight":0}}}},{"id":"si10674","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_135","title":"B) ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si10678","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_136","title":"Patients on multiple medications ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si10678","class":"TODO::Senthil","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button","question":"Slide10788q1"},"answer":{"title":"dummy title","index":-1,"score":{}}}},{"id":"si10674_a","class":"TODO::Senthil","roles":{"answer":{"title":"Patients on multiple medications\r","index":"Not implemented","score":{"weight":0}}}},{"id":"si11425","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"C) ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si11429","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"Patients on inappropriate medications ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si11429","class":"TODO::Senthil","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button","question":"Slide10788q1"},"answer":{"title":"dummy title","index":-1,"score":{}}}},{"id":"si11425_a","class":"TODO::Senthil","roles":{"answer":{"title":"Patients on inappropriate medications\r","index":"Not implemented","score":{"weight":0}}}},{"id":"si11839","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"D) ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si11843","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"No single health provider overseeing all care ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si11843","class":"TODO::Senthil","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"button","question":"Slide10788q1"},"answer":{"title":"dummy title","index":-1,"score":{}}}},{"id":"si11839_a","class":"TODO::Senthil","roles":{"answer":{"title":"No single health provider overseeing all care\r","index":"Not implemented","score":{"weight":0}}}},{"id":"si10727","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Button_22","title":"Check Your Answer ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"submit","question":"Slide10788q1","for":"Slide10788q1"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si10789","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"Back ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"back","question":"Slide10788q1","for":"Slide10788q1"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si11678","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"Next Question ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"skip","question":"Slide10788q1","for":"Slide10788q1"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si11751","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"Clear ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"clear","question":"Slide10788q1","for":"Slide10788q1"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si10739","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_141","title":"You must answer the question before continuing. ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si10751","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_142","title":"Sorry, that’s incorrect.  Answers A, B, C, and D are correct.  Please see Lesson 1, Topic 1, Page 2: Drug-Related Problems (DRPs).  Click “Next Question” to continue. ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si10763","class":"TODO::Senthil","instance":"Text_Caption_143","title":"That’s Correct !  Click “Next Question” to continue.  ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si11771","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"Good try, but you have not selected all the answers.  Please see Lesson 1, Topic 1, Page 2: Drug-Related Problems (DRPs).  Click here to continue, then click the Clear button to try again. ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"Slide10788","class":"Question Slide","instance":"","thumbnail":"","children":["si10640","si10652","si10667","si10678","si11429","si11843","si10727","si10789","si11678","si11751","si10739","si11771"],"roles":{"slide":{"durationInFrames":90},"navigation":{"navid":"Slide10788"},"question":{"interactionId":"10619","quizId":455,"title":"Multiple Choice, Multiple Answers\r","text":"Red flags for drug-related problems (DRPs) include: (select all that apply)\r\r\r","ikc":false,"type":"graded","interactionType":"choice","ramdomized":false,"correctAnswers":["A","B","C","D"],"score":{"weight":10,"penalty":0}}}},{"id":"si10456","class":"TODO::Senthil","roles":{}},{"id":"si10397","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"True/False ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si10406","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"The estimated cost of inappropriate medication use and their consequences in the geriatric population is about $200 billion/year. ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si10421","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"A) ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si10425","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"True ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si10421_a","class":"TODO::Senthil","roles":{"answer":{"title":"True","index":"Not implemented","score":{"weight":0}}}},{"id":"si10432","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"B) ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si10436","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"False ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si10432_a","class":"TODO::Senthil","roles":{"answer":{"title":"False","index":"Not implemented","score":{"weight":0}}}},{"id":"si10460","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"Check Your Answer ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"submit","question":"Slide10371q2","for":"Slide10371q2"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si10492","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"Back ","roles":{"click":{"subtype":"back","question":"Slide10371q2","for":"Slide10371q2"},"textData":{}}},{"id":"si10440","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"That’s Correct !  Click the next button at the bottom of the screen to continue.  ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si10444","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"Sorry, that’s incorrect. The correct answer is TRUE.  Please see Lesson 1, Topic 1, Page 2: Drug-Related Problems (DRPs).  Click the next button at the bottom of the screen to continue. ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"si10448","class":"TODO::Senthil","title":"You must answer the question before continuing. ","roles":{"textData":{}}},{"id":"Slide10371","class":"Question Slide","instance":"","thumbnail":"","children":["si10397","si10406","si10425","si10436","si10460","si10492","si10448"],"roles":{"slide":{"durationInFrames":90},"navigation":{"navid":"Slide10371"},"question":{"interactionId":"10384","quizId":455,"title":"True/False","text":"The estimated cost of inappropriate medication use and their consequences in the geriatric population is about $200 billion/year.\r","ikc":false,"type":"graded","interactionType":"true-false","ramdomized":false,"correctAnswers":["A"],"score":{"weight":10,"penalty":0}}}},{"id":"Pool499","class":"pool","roles":{"pool":{"id":499,"name":"Pool1","questions":[]}}},{"id":"L1T2P1","class":"project","title":"L1T2P1","children":["Slide10992","Slide7447","Slide10788","Slide10371"],"roles":{"quiz":{"id":455,"branched":false,"submitAll":false,"review":true,"questions":["Slide7447q0","Slide10788q1","Slide10371q2"],"minScore":0,"maxScore":30,"passScore":21}}}],"contentSettings":{"global":{"branchAware":false},"toc":{"enabled":false},"playbar":{"enabled":false,"cc":false,"playPause":true,"back":true,"forward":true,"rewind":true,"close":true,"mute":true,"progressBar":true}},"contentReporting":{"CCCriteria":"quiz","CCData":{"quizData":"quiz_passed"},"SCCriteria":"quiz","SCData":{"quizData":"quiz_passed"},"exitNormalIfCompleted":false},"toc":[{"id":"Slide10992","title":"Slide 2"},{"id":"Slide7447","title":"Slide 3"},{"id":"Slide10788","title":"Slide 4"},{"id":"Slide10371","title":"Slide 5"}]}